(Raj:)Milk Dud?
(Zack:)Oh, I love Milk Duds.
(Zack:)Okay, we're cool.
(Raj:)Junior Mints.
(Zack:)You guys want to come in
and have a beer?
(Leonard:)Uh, we're on our way
to the comic book store.
(Howard:)Leonard's buying.
(Zack:)Really?
(Zack:)I haven't been
to a comic book store
(Zack:)in literally
a million years.
(Sheldon:)Literally?
(Zack:)Literally a
million years?
(Leonard:)Don't.
(Zack:)You want to go with 'em?
No.
(Zack:)Okay, see you later.
Wait,
w-w-w-wait, you're ditching me
to go look at comic books?
(Zack:)Are you mad at me?
(Penny:)I'm not happy.
(Raj:)Milk Dud?
(Zack:)Wow, this place
is awesome.
Where do they keep
the Archies?
(Sheldon:)In the bedrooms of ten-year-
old girls, where they belong.
Oh, no, you're thinking
old-school Archie.
(Zack:)It's much more
sophisticated now.
(Zack:)Like, there's
two universes,